Aditya Pratap Singh Bhadauriya (1) Featured



Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Software Testing, Coding, ASP. Net MVC, WPF, C#, MS SQL Server, Ajax, Javascript, JQuery, JSON, Python, Angular Js



Current Designation: Senior Software Engineer Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: CIGNEX Datamatics Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Gurgaon Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Delhi / NCR

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Software Developer, Team/Tech Lead, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Software Testing, Coding, ASP. Net MVC, WPF, C#, MS SQL

Server, Ajax, Javascript, JQuery, JSON, Python, Angular Js

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Summary

Skilled professional with 6 years of experience in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Software Testing, Coding, ASP. Net MVC, WPF, C#, MS SQL Server, Ajax, Javascript, JQuery, JSON, Python, Angular Js

Work Experience

CIGNEX Datamatics as Senior Software Engineer

Apr 2020 to Till Date

Working as senior software engineer

Hitach MGRM Net Ltd as Software Developer

Jan 2020 to Apr 2020

Worked as full stack .Net developer

Aakash Informatics as Software Developer

Apr 2017 to Apr 2020

Software developer with 5.8 Years of experience in .Net c# MVC, Web API, JavaScript, Jquery, CSS.

I engineering soft pvt ltd

Nov 2014 to Apr 2017

Hitech Infosoft as Junior Software Developer

Nov 2013 to Nov 2014

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Laxminarayan institute. of technology , Gwalior in 2012

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Microsoft SQL Server 2005,2008	
C#,ASP.Net,MVC,WPF	
HTML5,CSS3,Bootstrap design	
AJAx,Javascript,Json	
Web Api,Jquery Angular	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Projects

Project Title: BMS

Client: Porsche, Hyundai, Voksagen, Genesis, KIA motors, Volvo, Mazda

Nature of Employment: Full Time
Project Location: Ahmedabad
Role: Programmer

Duration: May 2017 - Till Date
Onsite / Offsite: Offsite
Team Size: 10

Skill Used: C#, MVC Architecture, Javascript, HTML, CSS

Role Description: Working as a developer

Project Details: This is project for business management gives service for dealership management for motor vehicle

companies

Project Title: ALIS Client: Policy makers

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Dec 2014 - Mar 2017
Project Location: Ahmedabad Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Role: Programmer Team Size: 14

Skill Used: C#

Project Details: Alis is the product like policy bazaar and gives service to Insurance company in Us market

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time